<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pitch patch</title>
    <link>https://pitchpatch.de/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on pitch patch</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pitchpatch.de/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PS: Knobula Poly Cinematic &#43; SoundForce uDCO, Torso T-1, and Elektron Model: Cycles Eurorack Jam</title>
      <link>https://pitchpatch.de/blog/posts/poly-cinematic-jam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pitchpatch.de/blog/posts/poly-cinematic-jam/</guid>
      <description>Watch two uncut Eurorack modular synth jams with Knobula Poly Cinematic, SoundForce uDCO, Torso T-1, and Elektron Model: Cycles.
The Poly Cinematic is an 8-voice polysynth Eurorack module designed to produce luscious pads and rhythmic power chords using just a few simple controls.
Grab the Poly Cinematic at Perfect Circuit https://pitchpat.ch/perfectcircuit-poly
Modules (FLTR) Knobula Poly Cinematic https://pitchpat.ch/perfectcircuit-poly SoundForce uDCO https://pitchpat.ch/perfectcircuit-udco ALM Busy Circuits Pip Slope Mk2 https://pitchpat.ch/perfectcircuit-pip Intellijel Rainmaker https://pitchpat.ch/reverb-rainmaker Intellijel USB Power 1U https://pitchpat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The First-Ever Pitch Patch Video: 4ms Ensemble Oscillator</title>
      <link>https://pitchpatch.de/blog/posts/polyphonic-eurorack-the-4ms-ensemble-oscillator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pitchpatch.de/blog/posts/polyphonic-eurorack-the-4ms-ensemble-oscillator/</guid>
      <description>As covid gifted me with more free time (and reamp labs has been on hold for the past two years) I started a new Youtube channel called pitch patch. I will be posting videos about music-making, tutorials, reviews, and demos.
In the first-ever pitch patch video, I go through all knobs and functions and show you two patch ideas of the 4ms Ensemble Oscillator.
The Ensemble Oscillator was designed by Matthias Puech and 4ms Company and is a polyphonic voice of sixteen sine-based oscillators combining additive, FM, phase-distortion, and wave folding synthesis techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://pitchpatch.de/blog/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pitchpatch.de/blog/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi There I am Michael and I make videos about synths and cool stuff.
If you
want to know all about a certain piece of gear
dont like reading manuals
want to get inspired
or just like listening to music
this channel (and blog) is for you! Feel free to check out my blog posts, videos, and pitcures.
Contact me if you have any questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://pitchpatch.de/blog/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pitchpatch.de/blog/contact/</guid>
      <description>I Would Love to Hear From You If you have any questions or inquiries, you can DM me on Instagram or send an email to website@pitchpat.ch.
Interested in collaborating? If you have a product and want to promote it, I would love to hear from you!
Among other things, I make
product demos and jams that showcase the potential of products in-depth walkthroughs that explain the features unboxing videos and short clips that get people excited!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>https://pitchpatch.de/blog/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pitchpatch.de/blog/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support</title>
      <link>https://pitchpatch.de/blog/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pitchpatch.de/blog/support/</guid>
      <description>Big Hug if You Consider Supporting pitch patch!
This channel (and blog) exists only because of you. You can support pitch patch by subscribing on YouTube, following on Instagram, or buy me a coffee.
If you head out to buy stuff pls use one of the following affiliate links. I get a small kickback at no extra cost to you. No data about you is collected, stored, used, or shared!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Use</title>
      <link>https://pitchpatch.de/blog/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pitchpatch.de/blog/terms/</guid>
      <description>Terms of Use Service Provider pitch patch
Boschetsrieder Str. 28
81379 München
Germany
Contact E-Mail: website@pitchpat.ch
Contact page: hello.pitchpat.ch
Journalistic-Editorial Offerings Content responsibility: Michael Schwartze
Audiovisual mMdia Services Country of domicile: Germany
Responsible regulatory or supervisory authority: Bavarian Regulatory Authority for Commercial Broadcasting (BLM).
Social Media and Other Online Presence This legal notice also applies to the following social media presences and online profiles:
Instagram.com/realpitchpatch
Youtube.com/pitchpatch
Disclaimer, Liability, and Property Rights Information Responsibility for Contents The contents of our web pages were created with the greatest care.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
